Christmas with Holly is a drama, family, tv movie film directed by Allan Arkush.
After being dumped at the altar on her wedding day, Maggie Conway moves to the island town of Friday
Harbor in Washington State, where she meets Mark Nagle, the local coffee shop owner.
Mark Nagle, played by Sean Faris.
Maggie Conway, played by Eloise Mumford.
Holly Nagle, played by Lucy Gallina.
Scott Nagle, played by Dana Watkins.
Alex Nagle, played by Daniel Eric Gold.
Cara, played by Vanessa Matsui.
Christmas with Holly is a 2012 made-for-TV film starring Eloise Mumford and Sean Faris
based on the 2010 book Christmas Eve at Friday Harbor by Lisa Kleypas.
It originally aired on ABC as a Hallmark Hall of Fame film on December 9, 2012.
The tone is emotional.